<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>blog.jfo.click</title>
    <link>https://blog.jfo.click</link>
    <description>Recent content on blog.jfo.click</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <image>
      <title>blog.jfo.click</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click</link>
      <url>https://blog.jfo.click/desk.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed Jul 13 2022 14:08:02 GMT+0200 (Central European Summer Time)</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An Unnamed Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/an-unnamed-static-site-generator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>I wrote a static site generator; to dispense with the &quot;why.&quot;</p>
<p>This blog has been, in order, wordpress, middleman, jekyll, and hugo. Each time
I become comfortable with one, inevitably they will become too slow for my
needs (jekyll) or introduce subtle, minute breaking changes into some version
or another, offering me an opportunity to jump ship (middleman and hugo) or
just be not fit for purpose / total overkill (wordpress). I ...]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.jfo.click/an-unnamed-static-site-generator</guid>
      <pubDate>Jul 13, 2022</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week two point two</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/week-two-point-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Week two! I spend a lot less time shaving yaks, which is good. Though I am
still trying to get around to a few more improvements there...</p>
<p>This week was both frustrating and satisfying... frustrating because I don&#39;t
feel like I really <em>completed</em> anything, but satisfying because I managed to
get unstuck a few times off really big challenges.</p>
<p>I spent a fair bit of time trying to implement parser combinators and made it
<...]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.jfo.click/week-two-point-two</guid>
      <pubDate>Jul 09, 2022</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ur-question of Blogging</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/the-ur-question-of-blogging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>{{#img}}
beach.jpg
{{/img}}</p>
<p>Until my couple of recent posts, it had been a long while since I had posted
anything.  There were good reasons for this...  and bad reasons.</p>
<p>The good reasons are pretty standard issue. In mid 2017, I started a new job,
had a baby, and moved to a new country within a few weeks. Between all those
things going on all at once it was tough to make the time and spend the energy
on writing very many substant...]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.jfo.click/the-ur-question-of-blogging</guid>
      <pubDate>Jul 04, 2022</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
